canon.com.my 2018-09-03

# Privacy policy - Canon Malaysia

## Acceptance

This website ("Canon Website") is provided to you by Canon Marketing (Malaysia) Sdn. Bhd ("Canon") on the following terms and conditions ("Terms and Conditions"). By accessing any page on this Canon Website, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions may be updated by Canon from time to time without prior notice. You should check the Terms and Conditions for updates each time you access the Canon Website.  

## Our Commitment To Privacy

As your privacy is important to us, we provide this Statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. For easy accessibility, this Statement will be made available on our homepage and on every page of our website.  

## Scope

This Statement covers all aspects of Canon Website on which our privacy statement hyperlink appears. The information covered by this Statement is personal information an individual provides to Canon outside of his/her trade, business or profession ("Information").  

## The Information We Collect

There are two forms of Information that Canon collects online: Website Visitorship Information and Personal Identifiable Information voluntarily provided to Canon by Canon Website visitors.

**Website Visitorship Information**  
Canon gathers Information on Website activity, such as data on the number of people who visit the Canon Website, the pages they visit, the duration of their stay, etc. Website Visitorship Information is:

  * Collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means no Personal Identifiable Information is associated with this data;
  * Gathered through the use of web server logs and cookies.

**Personal Identifiable Information**  
Personal Identifiable Information is collected on certain pages of the Canon Website. If you contact Canon online to ask a question, post a feedback, register a recently-purchased product, inquire about products you may already own, or participate in voluntary online surveys, you will find that those contact forms ask for certain types of Personal Identifiable Information to assist us in complying with your requests.

  * Canon may ask you to provide Personal Identifiable Information, on specific pages of the Canon Website. The information requested may include your name, address, e-mail address, contact number, product model and serial numbers and the dates of purchase, and your comments. Personal Identifiable Information may be forwarded to a Canon business unit or the appropriate Canon headquarters, subsidiary or affiliate company that is equipped to handle your inquiry or feedback.  

Personal Identifiable Information is collected only when Canon Website visitors voluntarily provide it and such information is not necessary to simply browse the Canon Website.  

## How We Use Information

We use the Information you provide about yourself to perform the service you have requested and may use that Information to provide you with information about other Canon products and promotions that may be of interest to you. Your Information may be shared among our employees, agents or other related and unrelated Canon entities and/or business partners acting on our behalf to conduct surveys or to provide a product or service you have requested. We do not share this information with non-Canon companies except to the extent necessary to complete your requests and, in the event we do share it, it is subject to their agreement to treat it as confidential business information and with the understanding that it may not be used for any purpose other than to perform their function. If you inquire about a product that Canon does not sell directly, we may forward your information to a Canon authorized dealer, distributor or other reseller. Use of your information by the authorized dealer, distributor or reseller is governed by its own policies, not Canon's. Canon may also provide links to dealer sites from the Canon Website. See our discussion below and in our Terms of Use about further information about such links.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive as well as to provide you with product and service updates, special promotions and offers.

In the course of growing or restructuring our business, we may purchase the assets of another company or sell the assets of our company. During these transactions, information about customers is frequently considered a business asset that is the subject of such a purchase or sale. Also, in the unlikely event that Canon, or substantially all of its assets are either acquired or subject to liquidation in bankruptcy, Information may be transferred as well.

The Canon Website may contain hyperlinks to and from other Internet websites, including other Canon Company websites. These websites may have different privacy practices from the ones described here. Since this Statement applies solely to this Website, please read the privacy statements of the other websites you visit. For more information about hyperlinks, please see the Terms of Use posted elsewhere on our Canon Website.

We release Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Canon, Canon Website users or others. This includes exchanging Information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

Canon strives to ensure that our systems are secure and that they meet industry standards. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the Information we collect online. The security of personal information you may submit in connection with a promotion entry, survey response, and/or registration for any feature on the Canon Website is of the utmost concern to us, and we strive to ensure its security on our systems. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk. We will continue to assess new technology to evaluate its ability to provide additional protection of your Information.

##   
Right to Amend our Online Privacy Statement

Canon reserves the right to amend this Statement at any time. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website.

##   
NOTICE UNDER THE PERSONAL DATA PROTECTION ACT 2010

**_NOTICE UNDER THE PERSONAL DATA PROTECTION ACT 2010_**

_English version_

_Revision No. 01_

_Updated on 1 st August 2018_

The Personal Data Protection Act 2010 (hereinafter referred to as “the Act”), which regulates the processing of personal data in commercial transactions, applies to Canon Marketing (Malaysia) Sdn Bhd, and the Canon Asia Marketing Group (“CAMG”) (collectively referred to as “our”, “us” or “we”). For the purposes of this Notice, the terms “personal data” and “processing” shall have the same meaning as prescribed in the Act.

  1. This written notice serves to inform you that your personal data is being processed by us or on our behalf.
  2. The personal data processed by us may include without limitation your name, NRIC No., contact details such as telephone number and correspondence address, financial and banking account details provided by you in the documents as prescribed in paragraph 4 of this Notice and all other details relating thereto.  It may also include your images or recordings taken during our private or public events or activities.
  3. We are processing your personal data, including any additional information you may subsequently provide, for the following purposes (“Purposes”) :

  1. to carry out our obligations related to the sales and/or the provision of our products and/or services to you including without limitation keeping track of your purchase and warranty and to provide you support on our products purchased/rented by you;
  2. for communication with you regarding a variety of information on products and services, sales and/or general administration purposes;
  3. to maintain and update our customer service records;
  4. for statistical records and analysis;
  5. to carry out promotional and marketing activities;
  6. to promote and provide you with information related to our products and services unless you have otherwise indicated that you do not wish for us to process your personal data for such purpose; and such other purposes as may be related to the foregoing.  

  1. In the event you provide us an alternative contact detail and/or contact person, you hereby confirm and acknowledged that you are responsible in obtaining the consent of such person as an alternative contact detail and/or contact person in order for us to process for the above Purposes.
  2. Your personal data is and will be collected from you and/or from the information you have provided in your emails, all application/registration forms, information that you may provide us from time to time via oral communications and written communications and information provided by third parties such as credit information provider and our business partners.   
  3. Your personal data may be disclosed to parties such as but not limited to our related corporations, banks, auditors, governmental departments and/or agencies, regulatory and/or statutory bodies, credit check companies, business partners, service providers, our manufacturers and any such third party requested or authorised by you for any of the above Purposes or any other purpose for which your personal data was to be disclosed at the time of its collection or any other purpose directly related to any of the above Purposes.
  4. If you fail to supply to us the above personal data or subsequently withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal data, we may not be able to process your personal data for any of the above Purposes.
  5. We may transfer your personal data to a place outside Malaysia and you hereby give your consent to the transfer.
  6. You are responsible for ensuring that the personal data you provide us is accurate, complete and not misleading and that such personal data is kept up to date.
  7. In the event of any inconsistency between the English version and the Bahasa Malaysia version of this notice, the English version shall prevail over the Bahasa Malaysia version.
  8. You may access and request for updating and correction of your personal data and to contact us with any enquiries or complaints in respect of your personal data as follows:- 

Contact Person:

| 

Customer Support

| 

Telephone No.:

| 

03-5568 2333  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
E-mail address:

| 

CMM_CustomerSupport@cmm.canon.com.my

| 

Facsimile No.:

| 

03-5567 9441  
  
If you wish to withdraw your consent and to unsubscribe from any future correspondences, please email us, otherwise we assume that you agree to our processing of your personal data in accordance with the above.

**_NOTIS DI BAWAH AKTA PERLINDUNGAN DATA PERIBADI 2010_**

_Versi Bahasa Melayu_

_No.Semakan 01_

_Dikemaskini pada 1 Ogos 2018_

Akta Perlindungan Data Peribadi 2010 (selepas ini disebut sebagai “Akta”), yang mengawal selia pemprosesan data peribadi untuk tujuan transaksi komersial, adalah terpakai terhadap Canon Marketing (Malaysia) Sdn Bhd dan Canon Asia Marketing Group (“CAMG”) (selepas ini disebut sebagai “kami”). Untuk tujuan Notis ini, terma-terma “data peribadi” dan “pemprosesan” akan mempunyai maksud seperti yang ditakrifkan di dalam Akta.

  1. Notis bertulis ini bertujuan untuk memaklumkan kepada anda bahawa data peribadi anda sedang diproses oleh atau bagi pihak kami.
  2. Data peribadi yang diproses oleh kami termasuk tanpa had nama, nombor kad pengenalan, maklumat perhubungan seperti nombor telefon, alamat surat-menyurat, butiran kewangan dan akaun perbankan anda, yang diberikan oleh anda dalam dokumen-dokumen yang dinyatakan dalam perenggan 4 Notis ini dan sebarang butiran-butiran lain yang berkaitan dengannya. Ia juga termasuk imej anda atau rakaman yang diambil semasa acara dan aktiviti tertutup atau terbuka yang dianjurkan oleh kami.
  3. Kami sedang memproses data peribadi anda, termasuklah sebarang maklumat tambahan yang anda mungkin berikan kemudian, untuk tujuan-tujuan berikut (“Tujuan-Tujuan”):

  1. untuk menjalankan tanggungjawab kami yang berkaitan dengan jualan dan/atau pembekalan produk dan/atau perkhidmatan kami kepada anda seperti dan tidak hanya terhad kepada untuk mengesan pembelian dan jaminan anda dan memberi anda penyelenggaraan servis untuk produk kami yang dibeli/disewa oleh anda ;
  2. untuk berkomunikasi dengan anda tentang pelbagai maklumat mengenai produk dan perkhidmatan, jualan dan / atau tujuan pentadbiran am;
  3. untuk mengekalkan dan mengemaskini rekod perkhidmatan pelanggan kami;
  4. untuk rekod-rekod statistik dan analisis;
  5. untuk menjalankan aktiviti promosi dan pemasaran;
  6. untuk mempromosi dan memberikan anda maklumat berkenaan dengan produk-produk dan perkhidmatan-perkhidmatan kami selainkan anda sebaliknya menunjukkan bahawa anda tidak berniat untuk kami memproses data peribadi anda untuk tujuan tersebut dan bagi tujuan-tujuan lain yang mungkin berkaitan dengan perkara-perkara yang dinyatakan di atas.

  1. Sekiranya anda memberikan kami satu butiran alternatif orang untuk dihubungi, anda dengan ini mengesahkan dan mengakui bahawa anda adalah bertanggungjawab untuk mendapatkan persetujuan orang itu sebagai alternatif untuk dihubungi oleh pihak kami bagi membolehkan kami untuk memproses bagi Tujuan yang dinyatakan di atas.
  2. Data peribadi anda sedang dan akan dikumpulkan daripada anda dan/atau merangkumi segala maklumat yang anda berikan di dalam emel anda, semua borang permohonan/pendaftaran, maklumat-maklumat lain yang anda berikan melalui komunikasi lisan atau bertulis serta maklumat-maklumat yang diberikan oleh pihak-pihak ketiga seperti pembekal-pembekal informasi kredit dan rakan perniagaan kami .
  3. Data peribadi anda mungkin dizahirkan kepada pihak-pihak seperti dan tidak hanya terhad kepada syarikat-syarikat berkaitan kami, bank-bank, juru audit, semua jabatan dan/atau agensi kerajaan dan/atau kuasi-kerajaan, badan-badan penguatkuasa dan/atau berkanun, syarikat-syarikat pemeriksaan kredit, rakan-rakan perniagaan dan/atau pembekal-pembekal perkhidmatan, pengilang kami dan sebarang pihak ketiga yang lain yang mana anda telah minta atau memberikan kuasa kepada kami untuk menzahirkan data peribadi anda untuk tujuan-tujuan yang dinyatakan di atas atau sebarang tujuan lain yang mana data peribadi anda telah dizahirkan pada masa pengumpulannya atau untuk tujuan lain yang mempunyai hubungan secara langsung dengan mana-mana Tujuan-Tujuan yang dinyatakan di atas.
  4. Jika anda gagal untuk memberikan kepada kami data peribadi yang dinyatakan di atas atau menarik balik persetujuan anda untuk memproses data peribadi anda, kami mungkin tidak boleh memproses data peribadi anda untuk sebarang Tujuan-Tujuan yang dinyatakan di atas.
  5. Kami boleh memindahkan data peribadi anda ke sesuatu tempat di luar Malaysia dan anda dengan ini memberikan persetujuan anda terhadap pemindahan tersebut.
  6. Anda bertanggungjawab untuk memastikan bahawa data peribadi anda berikan kepada kami adalah tepat, lengkap, tidak mengelirukan dan data peribadi tersebut adalah yang terkini.
  7. Sekiranya terdapat sebarang ketidakseragaman di antara versi Bahasa Inggeris dan Bahasa Malaysia ke atas Notis ini, maka versi Bahasa Inggeris akan digunakan.
  8. Anda boleh mengakses dan memohon untuk mengemaskini atau membuat pembetulan data peribadi anda serta menghubungi kami untuk sebarang pertanyaan atau aduan berkenaan dengan data peribadi anda seperti berikut:

Individu Yang Perlu Dihubungi:

| 

CustomerSupport

| 

No. Telefon:

| 

03-5568 2333  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Alamat e-mel:

| 

CMM_CustomerSupport@cmm.canon.com.my

| 

No. Faksimili:

| 

03-5567 9441  
  
Jika anda ingin menarik balik persetujuan dan berhenti melanggan dari mana-mana koresponden pada masa hadapan, sila e-mel kepada kami, jika tidak, kami menganggap bahawa anda bersetuju untuk pemprosesan ke atas data peribadi anda seperti di atas.
